<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<newsSite>
    <articles>
        <article id="1">
            <title>New Game Release: Kingdom Come Deliverance 2</title>
            <metadata>
                <author>Dmytro Bailuk</author>
                <datePublished>2024-04-18</datePublished>
                <dateModified>2024-04-18</dateModified>
                <category>New Releases</category>
                <publisher>outGame</publisher>
            </metadata>
            <content>
                <summary>The sequel to the Czech historical RPG is here, featuring an overhauled combat system and expanded world.</summary>
                <details>
                    <point>Delve into a narrative rich in history and enhanced with a dynamic ecosystem that challenges even veteran players.</point>
                    <point>Explore vast landscapes and engage in more complex interactions with characters driven by sophisticated AI.</point>
                </details>
            </content>
            <editor>Jan Svoboda</editor>
        </article>
        <article id="2">
            <title>Overwatch 2 April Balance Patch</title>
            <metadata>
                <author>Alikhanov Miras</author>
                <datePublished>2024-04-17</datePublished>
                <dateModified>2024-04-17</dateModified>
                <category>Updates</category>
                <publisher>outGame</publisher>
            </metadata>
            <content>
                <summary>Blizzard's latest patch introduces a new map and adjusts character abilities to enhance gameplay balance.</summary>
                <details>
                    <point>The update aims to refine gameplay mechanics, focusing on fair play and competitive integrity.</point>
                    <point>Overwatch enthusiasts will find the game increasingly rewarding with these thoughtful balance tweaks.</point>
                </details>
            </content>
            <editor>Denis Kat</editor>
        </article>
        <article id="3">
            <title>Tips and Tricks for Winning in Fortnite</title>
            <metadata>
                <author>Jane Doe</author>
                <datePublished>2024-04-19</datePublished>
                <dateModified>2024-04-19</dateModified>
                <category>Strategy Guides</category>
                <publisher>outGame</publisher>
            </metadata>
            <content>
                <summary>Discover expert building strategies and weapon selection to dominate in Fortnite's dynamic battlefields.</summary>
                <details>
                    <point>Master the art of quick build battles and learn the secrets behind successful loot strategies that can give you an edge over the competition.</point>
                    <point>This guide offers essential tactics that are crucial for survival and victory.</point>
                </details>
            </content>
            <editor>Orest Kucher</editor>
        </article>
        <article id="4">
            <title>Cyberpunk 2077 Expansion Revealed</title>
            <metadata>
                <author>Casey Smith</author>
                <datePublished>2024-04-20</datePublished>
                <dateModified>2024-04-20</dateModified>
                <category>Announcements</category>
                <publisher>outGame</publisher>
            </metadata>
            <content>
                <summary>CD Projekt Red unveils a massive expansion for Cyberpunk 2077, promising new storylines and tech upgrades.</summary>
                <details>
                    <point>The expansion promises to address previous gameplay issues and expand the narrative to include new districts within Night City.</point>
                    <point>Fans can expect enhanced graphics and more immersive story elements that deepen the Cyberpunk experience.</point>
                </details>
            </content>
            <editor>Kirill Kisil</editor>
        </article>
        <article id="5">
            <title>League of Legends Season Update</title>
            <metadata>
                <author>Emily Nguyen</author>
                <datePublished>2024-04-22</datePublished>
                <dateModified>2024-04-22</dateModified>
                <category>Game Updates</category>
                <publisher>outGame</publisher>
            </metadata>
            <content>
                <summary>Riot Games rolls out the new season update for League of Legends, featuring major gameplay changes and character tweaks.</summary>
                <details>
                    <point>This update introduces new champions and rebalances existing ones to shake up the meta, aiming to improve the competitive scene and overall player engagement.</point>
                    <point>Innovative champion designs and smarter gameplay mechanics enhance the tactical aspects of the game.</point>
                </details>
            </content>
            <editor>Pavel Vovk</editor>
        </article>
    </articles>


    <reviews>
        <review id="1">
            <title>"Kingdom Come Deliverance 2" - A New Adventure Awaits</title>
            <metadata>
                <author>Toby Fox</author>
                <datePublished>2024-04-20</datePublished>
                <gameReviewed>Kingdom Come Deliverance 2</gameReviewed>
                <ratingValue>4.5</ratingValue>
                <bestRating>5</bestRating>
                <worstRating>1</worstRating>
                <publisher>outGame</publisher>
            </metadata>
            <reviewBody>
                <summary>Stunning graphics and an engaging storyline make this RPG a must-play.</summary>
                <details>
                    <point>Dive into a meticulously crafted world that blurs the line between reality and virtual, bringing medieval history to life with unprecedented detail.</point>
                </details>
            </reviewBody>
        </review>
        <review id="2">
            <title>Exploring the Universe in 'Starfield'</title>
            <metadata>
                <author>Lebron James</author>
                <datePublished>2024-04-21</datePublished>
                <gameReviewed>Starfield</gameReviewed>
                <ratingValue>4.2</ratingValue>
                <bestRating>5</bestRating>
                <worstRating>1</worstRating>
                <publisher>outGame</publisher>
            </metadata>
            <reviewBody>
                <summary>Bethesda's latest RPG offers a vast universe to explore, rich with diverse planets and lifeforms.</summary>
                <details>
                    <point>Experience the thrill of space exploration and the strategic depth of building alliances across galaxies.</point>
                </details>
            </reviewBody>
        </review>
        <review id="3">
            <title>"League of Legends Season Update" - Strategic Refresh</title>
            <metadata>
                <author>Conor McGregor</author>
                <datePublished>2024-04-22</datePublished>
                <gameReviewed>League of Legends</gameReviewed>
                <ratingValue>4.3</ratingValue>
                <bestRating>5</bestRating>
                <worstRating>1</worstRating>
                <publisher>outGame</publisher>
            </metadata>
            <reviewBody>
                <summary>The latest season update brings refreshing changes to the strategic depth of League of Legends.</summary>
                <details>
                    <point>With innovative champion designs and smarter gameplay mechanics, this update enhances the tactical aspects of the game, providing a fresh experience for veterans and newcomers alike.</point>
                </details>
            </reviewBody>
        </review>
    </reviews>
</newsSite>